export default [
  {
    title: 'Purchasing',
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'If I purchase AlgoExpert, how long do I have access to the product?',
        answer: '1 year.',
      },
      {
        question:
          "If I've already purchased AlgoExpert and you add more content to the platform, will I gain access to it for free?",
        answer:
          "Yes. Any new content that isn't specifically marketed as a separate product will be available to you for free (even if our price increases), so long as your access to the product hasn't expired. For example, new algorithm questions that we release will be available to you for free.",
      },
      {
        question: 'What is your refund policy?',
        answer:
          "We don't offer refunds under any circumstance. You can try out our 4 free questions to decide if you'd like to buy AlgoExpert.",
      },
      {
        question: 'My card is being declined. How can I buy AlgoExpert?',
        answer:
          'If your card is being declined, you can pay with PayPal or with a digital wallet like Apple Pay, Google Pay, or Microsoft Pay. Alternatively, you can try paying with other cards or contacting your bank to see if they can resolve the issue.',
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: 'Product',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Are there any prerequisites to AlgoExpert?',
        answer:
          "Beyond knowing the fundamentals of programming (for example: conditional statements, loops, and basic string manipulation), no. You'll learn everything else that you need to know for coding interviews by watching the videos on AlgoExpert.",
      },
      {
        question:
          "I'm a complete beginner when it comes to data structures and algorithms. Is AlgoExpert for me?",
        answer:
          'Yes. Our Data Structures Crash Course will teach you everything you need to know to tackle the coding interview questions on AlgoExpert.',
      },
      {
        question: 'You currently offer 85 questions. Will you be adding more?',
        answer:
          "Yes. Our ultimate goal is to offer 100 questions. While we can't provide an exact date for when we'll release new questions, we can assure you that we're hard at work producing them! You can expect incremental releases of 5 new questions at a time.",
      },
      {
        question:
          'The coding-walkthrough portion of your videos is filmed in Python. Will you ever provide videos in another language?',
        answer:
          "No. Python is widely recognized as the easiest programming language to learn. Its simplicity makes it the most accessible choice for our video explanations. Our written solutions provide the language-specific clarity that you're likely seeking.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: 'Common Issues',
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          "I've purchased AlgoExpert, but I no longer have access to the product. What's wrong?",
        answer:
          "You're likely logged in on a different account than the one you purchased AlgoExpert on, or you're not logged in at all. Make sure that you're logged in, and try all of your known Google, Facebook, and GitHub accounts. If the problem persists, contact us.",
      },
      {
        question: `I can't watch videos on AlgoExpert because of "privacy settings." What's wrong?`,
        answer:
          "This is due to a browser extension or some other software that you're using. Try disabling all browser extensions and other software that might block certain things online.",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    title: 'Other',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Is AlgoExpert worth it?',
        answer:
          "Unequivocally, yes. Let's look at an example to explain. In cities like NYC or SF, top companies give total-compensation packages of about $170,000 for entry-level Software Engineers, mid-tier companies give total-compensation packages of about $110,000, and low-tier companies give packages of about $70,000. Assume that you can get an offer from a low-tier company without AlgoExpert. Then, assume that AlgoExpert only gives you a 50% chance of getting a mid-tier offer and a 20% chance of getting a high-tier offer. Your expected payoff from AlgoExpert is a whopping $40,000 ($100,000 * 0.2 + $40,000 * 0.5), and the price of AlgoExpert becomes absolutely meaningless.",
      },
      {
        question: `I've seen other interview-prep resources that cost more than triple the price of AlgoExpert. How come?`,
        answer:
          "As is explained in our answer above, the expected payoff of AlgoExpert is very high. That means AlgoExpert could command a much higher price. However, having been in the grueling job-search process ourselves, we know that the last thing you want to do right now is to spend hundreds of dollars, especially if you're currently a student or out of a job. That's why AlgoExpert is so cheap.",
      },
      {
        question: `Will AlgoExpert help me land coding interviews?`,
        answer:
          "AlgoExpert will help you prepare for coding interviews. Unfortunately, landing interviews is a different ball game entirely. We'd recommend checking out this video that Cl√©ment made about how he landed his interviews at Google.",
      },
    ],
  },
];
